Guide to the Clive L. DuVal papers, 1960-1994
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: Legislative Files, 1966-1992
  - Subseries 2.1 - Congressional Bills, 1966-1992; (68 Boxes)
    - Falls Church, undated (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Gasoline Service Station Operators, undated (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - General Obligation Bonds, undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Giarratano Case, undated (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Income Tax Payments, Expediting Deposits by Commissioners of Revenues and Treasurers, SB857, undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Landlord/Tenant Act Amendment, SB878, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Late Payment Penalties Personal Property Taxes, SB817, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Lottery Proceeds, Distribution of, HB1867, undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk/Southern Railroad Track Resolution, SJR250, undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - George Mason University (GMU), undated (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - J. Lambert Commending Resolution, undated (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Practice of Law by Military Attorneys, SB594, undated (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Reorganization of State Government, undated (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Real Estate Assessments - Limitations on Annual Increase (Constitutional Amendment), undated (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Rules, undated (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Sales Tax Acceleration, SB818, undated (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Senate Finance Committee, undated (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Storm Water Management, HB1770, undated (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - United Airlines Facility (pt 1), SB900, undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - United Airlines Facility (pt 2), SB900, undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - United Airlines, 1990-1991 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Authority to Issue Virginia Revenue Bonds, SB1506, undated (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Eminent Domain Grants Power to Loudon Authority for Construction Aircraft Hanger and Maint. Facility, SB1505, undated (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - SB1507, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Canons of Judicial Conduct for Virginia / ABA Code of Judicial Conduct, undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Reapportionment Case (pt 1), 1971 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Reapportionment Case (pt 2), 1971 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Reapportionment Case (pt 3), 1971 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Reapportionment Case (pt 4), 1971 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Reapportionment Case (pt 5), 1971 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Reapportionment Case (pt 6), 1971 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Tax Differential, SB180, undated (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Real Estate CAP 8% / CPI, SB327, undated (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Budget: Housing Partnership Fund, undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Bottle Bill, SB256, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Gasoline Service Station Bill, SB235, undated (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Oil Spills, SB411, undated (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Water Pollution (Discharges) Tougher Controls, SB465, undated (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Local Option Income Tax, SB173, undated (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - 1990 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Binding Arbitration / Elected School Boards, undated (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Budget Amendment, undated (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Budget: W and OD Trail Bridge, undated (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Infertility: Jones, undated (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Marina Motor Fuel Taxes, SB212, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Physical Therapists: Expanding Scope of Practice and Dental Hygienists, undated (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Relief of M. Boyd Jones Claims Committee, SB65, undated (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Semi-Personal, undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Surrogacy/Abortion Parental Notification, undated (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Downsizing, undated (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Drive Right Hodges, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Drug Abuse, undated (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Drunk Driving, undated (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Goat Farmers: Black and Ware, undated (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Recreational Opportunities - State Parks, undated (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Recycling: Arlington County, undated (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Montpelier, Residential School for the Gifted, HJR119, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Higher Education in Northern Virginia Study, SJR90, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Housing Study Commission, HB1050, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Public Authority - Transportation, undated (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Session, CLD Bills, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Legislative Session, CLD Bills, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Bank Service-Fee Charges, Checks Held, undated (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Bottle Bill, undated (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Linda Chernsky, undated (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Child Support Enforcement, undated (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Christian Fellowship Church, undated (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Churchill Road and Delf Drive Beltway Noise Problem, undated (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - C and P Refund, 1986 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Clean Air Act, 1986 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Commuter Rail, undated (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Concealed Weapon Bill, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Conservation Easement Act, undated (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Constitutional Convention, undated (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Contractors - Problems with Hills, undated (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Crime in Virginia, undated (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Assessments - Real Estate - Fairfax County (pt 1), undated (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Assessments - Real Estate - Fairfax County (pt 2), undated (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Assessments - Real Estate - Fairfax County (pt 3), undated (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Memec, Miss Linda, undated (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Tourism, undated (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Taxes - Dem/GDP Squabble over Surplus Taxes, undated (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Virginians for Dulles, undated (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Attorney General Opinions, undated (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Banks vs. Insurance Legislation, undated (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Legislation, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Legislation, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Lottery, undated (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Local Retirement Systems, Procedures for Reviewing, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Dulles Toll Road, undated (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Proffer Legislation, HB721, undated (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Shenandoah Geriatric Center, undated (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - "George Mason Lectures" - Honoring the 200th Anniversary of Virginia's Declaration of Rights, undated (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - GOP Tax, Transportation Proposals, undated (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Gypsy Moths, undated (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Gun Control, undated (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Human Resources Subcommittee, undated (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Head Injury Foundation, undated (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Fairfax County, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Fairfax County, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Gift Lot, undated (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Gift Lot, undated (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Mechanics Lien Law, undated (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Financial Planners, undated (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - McLean Social Studies, undated (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Mentally Ill, undated (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Mentally Ill, undated (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax County: Goals, undated (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Local Option Income Tax (pt 1), 1989 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Local Option Income Tax (pt 2), 1989 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Local Option Income Tax (pt 3), 1989 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Personal Property Taxation - Old Cars, undated (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Falls Hill, undated (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Old Courthouse Road, undated (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Occoquan Watershed Rezoning Decision, 1985 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Recordation Tax, undated (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Real Estate Appraisers, Study of (McCloud Hodges), undated (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Pornographic Magazines, Efforts to Restrict Sale, undated (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Pesticides and Chemicals, undated (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Outdoor Recreation Committee, undated (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - NCSL Government Operations and Pensions Committee, undated (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - NCSL - Human Services, undated (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Foundation, undated (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Kilheeney, Mrs. Mary Ann, undated (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Initiative and Referendum, undated (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Interest on Tax and Insurance Escrows, Mortgage Loans, undated (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Impact Fees, undated (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Board (pt 1), undated (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Board (pt 2), undated (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Board (pt 3), undated (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Cap. Citizens Against Airport Problems, undated (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Greater Washington Citizens for Dulles / Washington Airport Council, undated (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Dulles Airport Authority, pt 1, undated (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Dulles Airport Authority, pt 2, undated (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Dulles Airport Authority, pt 3, undated (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Dulles Airport Authority, pt 4, undated (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax County, undated (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - George Mason University (GMU), undated (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - High Speed Transportation System, undated (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Highway Funding Formulas, HBI169, undated (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Homestead Exemption, undated (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Lottery, undated (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - McLean Business District Undergoing Utility Lines, undated (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Metro, undated (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Milliken, Secretary of Transportation, undated (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Narfe, undated (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - National Environmental Policy: Federal Air and Water Pollution Law, undated (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - NCSL (AOL) State Government Issues and Organizations, 1990 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Non-Tidal Wetlands, pt 1, undated (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Non-Tidal Wetlands, pt 2, undated (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Noise Wall on Beltway Newr Churchill Road, undated (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Air and Space Museum Extension, SB323, undated (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Arlington County, undated (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Auto Emission Law, undated (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Beltway Widening, undated (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Bicycle Overpass Route 7 - Craig Day Part 1, undated (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Bicycle Overpass Route 7 - Craig Day Part 2, undated (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Budget Amendments, 1990-1992 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Cost Responsibility of Vehicles, SJR121, undated (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - County Day School, undated (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Disabled Retiree Benefits, undated (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Divestment, South Africa, CLD, undated (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Economic Development and Natural Resources, senate Subcommittee, undated (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Executive Budget Process, JLARC, 1991 (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Non-Tidal Wetlands Study, HB1037 Part 1, undated (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Non-Tidal Wetlands Study, HB1037 Part 2, undated (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Non-Tidal Wetlands Study Part 3, HB1037, undated (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Recycling Residues, Economical and Efficient Disposal Part 1, HJR384, undated (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Recycling Residues, Economical and Efficient Disposal Part 2, HJR384, undated (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Taxes - Federal Retiree's Income Part 1, undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Taxes - Federal Retiree's Income Part 2, undated (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Taxes - Federal Retiree's Income Part 3, undated (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Taxes - Federal Retiree's Income Part 4, undated (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Constitutional Convention Part 1, undated (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Constitutional Convention Part 2, undated (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Highway Program Financing - JLARC Part 1, SJR20, undated (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Highway Program Financing - JLARC Part 2, SJR20, undated (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Highway Program Financing - JLARC Part 3, SJR20, undated (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Water, undated (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Water and Sewer Services, HJR196, undated (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Economic Impact of State Regulations on Value of Private Property, HB1969, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Housing, SB474, undated (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Redistricting, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Transferable Development Rights and Taxation, SB711, undated (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - VMI Admissions, undated (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Delegation Meetings, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Executive Mansion, undated (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Judgeship Nominations, undated (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Medical Incinerators, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - Shindle, David - Claims Bill (Fisher), 1991 (Box 142, Folder 19)
    - State Corporation Commission Vacancy (Moore), undated (Box 142, Folder 20)
    - Income Taxation, Commissioner Option Re: Return, SB816, undated (Box 142, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Press Association, undated (Box 142, Folder 22)
    - Veto Session - Budget Matters, April 3, 1991 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Mechanic's Lien Laws, undated (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Abortion, undated (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Budget: Arts and Culture, undated (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Budget: Arts and Culture, undated (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Bottle Bill, undated (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1991 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Truck Accidents, undated (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Powercase, 1988 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Affairs, undated (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Vinson Hall Infirmary, undated (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Vodra, Richard E., Investment Advisor, undated (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Legislation Proposals - Where They Come From and How they Become Law, undated (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Comparative Price Advertisement Statute, HJR7184, 1990-1991 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - P and E Appointments Study Committee, 1991 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Budget: Department of Education, undated (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Delegation Meetings, 1990 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Senate P and E Appointments to Joint Studies and Commissions, 1990 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Georgetown Pike, undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Highway Problems: Fairfax County, undated (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Recycled Paper, undated (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Redistricting - State Ban on FX, undated (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Richards, Lilla - Constituent Problems, undated (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Route 28, undated (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Election of School Board in Virginia, undated (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Snow Removal, undated (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Taxation of Public Service Corps, undated (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Tax Reform Act, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Tidal Shoreline Erosion Policy, HJR46, undated (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Transfer Tax, undated (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Transportation Commission Re: Fairfax Bills, undated (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Amendments - TD Legislation Proposed by Governor, 1991 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Delegation Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Recommendations, undated (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Recommendations, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Higher Education Cuts, undated (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Reapportionment (After Supreme Court), undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Reapportionment Appeal, undated (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Reapportionment Appeal, undated (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Reapportionment Appeal, undated (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Voting Precincts: County of Fairfax Map, 1977 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Sub Census Tracts: County of Fairfax Map, 1977 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Reapportionment Appeal, undated (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Reapportionment Appeal, undated (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Redistricting Materials, undated (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Redistricting, 1980-1981 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax Voting Record, undated (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Redistricting, 1980-1981 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Redistricting, 1980-1981 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Acupuncture, SB174, 1990-1991 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Acupuncture, SB174, 1990-1991 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Acupuncture, SB174, 1990-1991 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Teachers in Grievances, HJR178, undated (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Materials Used in Virginia Power Point 1, undated (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Materials Used in Virginia Power Point 2, undated (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Vepco pt 1, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Vepco pt 2, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Bluffs of Wolftrap: Sound Barriers, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Dillon's Rule, undated (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Dulles Toll Road Sound Barriers, undated (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Dulles Toll Road High Occupancy Vehicle (HOV) Lanes, pt 1, SB808, undated (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Dulles Toll Road High Occupancy Vehicle (HOV) Lanes, pt 2, SB808, undated (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1966 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1968 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1970 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1971 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1973 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1974 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1974 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1975 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1976 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1977 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1978 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1979 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1980 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1981 (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1982 (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1983 (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 20)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 21)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1991 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1990 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1989 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1985 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1984 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1982 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1980 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1979 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1978 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1977 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1975 (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1974 (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1973 (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1972 (Box 158, Folder 20)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1971 (Box 158, Folder 21)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1970 (Box 158, Folder 22)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1968 (Box 158, Folder 23)
    - DuVal Bills and Resolutions, 1966 (Box 158, Folder 24)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1989 (Box 158, Folder 25)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1989 (Box 158, Folder 26)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 27)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 28)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1987 (Box 158, Folder 29)
    - Cosponsored Bills and Resolutions, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 30)
  - Subseries 2.2 - Legislative Studies, 1968-1992; (5 Boxes)
    This subseries contains studies on issues not necessarily linked to a specific bill. Such studies were used as background for developing a legislative agenda as well as for taking part in informed debate. Included in the studies are the major working files for the revision of the Virginia State Constitution (1968-1969) as well as information on such topics as the environment and nuclear energy regulation.
    - Constitution of Virginia, Report on the Commission on Constitutional Revision, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revision of C. L. DuVal proposals, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - CLD Constitutional Changes, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revision of, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revisions of: Positions, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revisions of: Summary (D. E. Howard), 1969 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revisions of: Natural, Historical and Cultural Resources, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revisions of: Conservative Amendment, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Bill of Rights: Assistance Counsel, Eavesdropping, etc., 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revisions of: Parallel Tables, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Constitution of Virginia: Revision of, Justification of Justification (A. E. Dick Howard), 1969 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revisions of: Proposed Constitutional Amendments, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revisions of: Referendum, 1970-1973 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - General Assembly of Virginia Manual of Senate and House of Delegates, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - State Corporation Committee Constitutional Revision, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Revisions of: Writings, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Nuclear Power Plants, Study of (CLD SJR136) [A], undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Nuclear Power Plants, Study of (CLD SJR136) [B], undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Nuclear Power Plants, Study of (CLD SJR136) [C], undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Outdoor Recreation Study Commission (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Critical Environment Areas, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Critical Environment Area, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - P and E Reapportionment [A], undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - P and E Reapportionment [B], undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - P and E Reapportionment [C], undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - P and E Reapportionment [D], undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court, Jurisdiction of, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Governor's Commission [A], 1986 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Governor's Commission [B], 1986 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Holton Commission - Airports, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Education, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax County; Authority to Build Secondary Roads, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Effects of Federal Budget Actions on the State of Virginia [conference], 1988 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Council of Higher Education Legislative Summary, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, undated (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Senate Finance (pt 1), 1989 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Senate Finance (pt 2), 1989 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Jamerson vs. Anderson - Suit to Invalidate Senator District in Final Plan, undated (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Senate Finance, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Senate Finance, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - VEPCO Rate Case (pt 1), 1987-1988 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - VEPCO Rate Case (pt 2), 1987-1988 (Box 112, Folder 4)